FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
5 YEARS AGO, SLOVAKIA
Brother Luca.
How are you feeling today?
I'm okay.
Thank you brother, for taking interest
in my well-being.
This is for you. I was in town earlier
and I heard them say that an Asian
man, like you
was going to perform tonight.
It might be good for you to see him.
You never know…
it might be what you need.
I think this will help you
regain
some of your memory.
Thank you.
N
Just like you told me. Freely.
It's all your fault!
Kang Pi-o.
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
EPISODE 8
JAE-IN ARE YOU UP?
PI-O, I'M SORRY
ARE YOU STILL MAD?
I'm not.
I'll call you later, okay?
SEND
Listen,
I know he's a genius and what not, but I
think it's a bit ridiculous to bring in
a twenty-seven-year-old as a conductor
for this orchestra.
Maestro Kang wouldn't just bring in
anyone.
Truth be told, I saw him at the Brno
competition and he was good.
He was good?
What's he good at?
Did he do a good job, or was it the
orchestra?
I mean… I guess we'll find out soon.
Hey, Jang Seok-hwan.
Are you bothered that your classmate
will be the conductor? Are you
jealous or something?
I'm not, come on.
I think we should test him. At measure
eleven, I'll go half a beat faster.
I'm certain… that he won't know Uh…
why the hell the sound seems off.
Who would notice that?
Only Maestro Kang.
Huh…
Hello, members of the orchestra.
As we had previously announced, our new
principal guest conductor, Luca
Domenico, will be leading all your
rehearsals as of today.
Now,
I would like to introduce you to your
Conductor.
Please come up.
Hello  everybody.
I'm Luca Domenico, and I…
am honored to be here.
We know his name is Choi Jeong-yo, why
introduce himself as Luca Dominico?
It's weird.
Let me say this in advance.
If you have any complaints or
suggestions, please talk to me directly.
If not, don't even bother
saying anything then.
The one and only thing we should be
discussing in the rehearsal room is
music. Are we clear on that?
Alright, then…
let's begin from the top of Brahms' first
movement.
One of the cellists
is late on the attack in measure eleven.
Principal Cello?
Oh. Um, that was totally my mistake.
I… I'm really sorry about it.
Uh… But…
I wasn't late on the attack.
I was early.
Well…
I guess you're not that precise, are you?
- No, you were late.
- I wasn't.
I was early.
You are a musician, like the rest of us.
But are you even aware of what a bad
habit you have?
Other players with the same habit you're
showing,
tend to drag the opening note
of a phrase.
So even if your bow moves first, the note
will still come in a beat behind.
This habit of yours
causes the sound to repeatedly
come in late.
The fact that you didn't even notice you
were doing it…
only proves to me that you are severely
out of practice.
And it compromises the sound of the whole
orchestra.
Just playing the cello doesn't make you
a good musician.
Put in the effort.
And practice.
Start again from the first movement.
Wow,
you're more experienced than I expected.
I knew you had a good ear, but how are
you so good at handling an orchestra too?
Oh… There's someone waiting to see you.
Waiting to see me?
Yes, exactly.
Choi…
Jeong-yo. Do you remember me?
I… used to teach you piano.
I'm Do Hyun-soo.
I'm so sorry, but I…
- I…
- It's okay.
Don't you worry about it.
Would it be okay if I gave you a hug?
Sure.
Hmm…
I'm sorry that I didn't come to see you
sooner.
You must be having a hard time
settling in here.
I thought I'd only make things worse,
so I…
waited to see you.
You know, after you went missing…
Ms. Yoon and I kept searching for
you for the longest time, but…
We could've never imagined you'd be…
at a monastery.
Why do all that for me?
You know, you were my student.
I care about you.
And also, because I was the one
who sent you there.
I felt terrible for not trying harder to
talk you out of it
ever since you came to me saying
that you wanted to compete.
You were perfectly happy doing music
on your own…
then I dragged you into it.
I regret doing that.
Still, I'm glad to see
the amazing man you've become.
I heard you told Ms. Yoon
that you were thinking of performing
a concerto with Pi-o.
Oh…
I saw a video of Mr. Kang Pi-o 's
performance and thought that we
might work well together.
You probably don't remember him.
Was it…
a coincidence, or did you have a gut
feeling about it?
Because back in high school,
Pi-o and you,
were really quite amazing playing
together.
I really hope you can convince Pi-o
and help him regain the confidence
to return to the stage.
Pi-o's been struggling lately. He's been
in a slump for quite a while.
I'm sure you know that.
MESSAGES NEW MESSAGE
CHOI JEONG-YO
Do you think we could meet?
Why don't you want to perform a concerto
with me?
Are you afraid of the stage? Or is
performing with me
what's uncomfortable.
To be honest with you,
it's both.
I'm sure you heard from Jae-in,
that I've made
a huge mistake
on stage recently.
I still haven't recovered from that.
I appreciate the opportunity,
but I think you should find someone else.
If that's the issue, your decision
doesn't make any sense.
- What do you mean?
- Think about it.
Well, the problem as I see it…
is that you can't just run away from
a slump.
The only way you can get through it
is to face it head-on.
Do you agree?
But you can't solve a problem by ignoring
it, you know that.
It's a hurdle you need to overcome,
sooner or later.
Thank you for the advice,
but I can handle it myself.
You better find someone else.
N
Welcome.
- I think we should celebrate.
- Table for two.
Please follow me, sir.
- Let's cheers to that!
- Are you being serious now?
- Yes I am!
- Oh, boy, Choi Jeong-yo.
You've always had a way of throwing
people for a loop.
Still, you should've told me about it. I
would've.
I nearly had a heart attack when I saw
the news!
You didn't need to worry, but I guess
you worried anyway.
How could I not worry about that?
You disappeared, never showed your face,
and now you're here.
How could I know you'd be fine?
So how's dad?
Oh… jeez.
He's absolutely fantastic!
Every time he sneaks out of the hospital
for a drink, I have to chase him down to
bring him back.
Man, I swear, I just don't understand why
you keep wasting your money on
that deadbeat.
Hey, by the way, tell me…
uh, when did you learn to do that?
You are…
just really good at everything you do.
If you hadn't been kidnapped,
you would've crushed that competition
too.
But hey man, why are you going around
telling people you've got amnesia?
Why not just expose them and put them
in jail?
And if that's not enough, we can go
find them and beat them ourselves.
Got it?
Hey,
I could maybe break two… of his fingers?
Or I could just make that bastard
disappear. I'm good with that.
Where's the fun in doing that?
Huh?
Well, don't you know that…
the waiting is worse… than the actual
beating?
N You've planned the whole thing already!
Come on, man, let me in on it.
What are you talking about?
Pi-o and Jeong-yo performing together?
I am absolutely against it.
Uh, really?
But why not?
I get why Pi-o wouldn't want to, but why
are you so against it?
Look, we haven't said anything to you,
but everyone knows that Pi-o's in a slump
right now.
His invitations are drying up, you know?
He's turned down the few we got so, yeah.
I'd say it's an issue.
Do you want to see Pi-o be forgotten
by the world?
Taking a break won't end his career.
Plenty of pianists have done just that.
Hey…
You can be honest with me.
Tell me why you hate this idea.
Is it because you don't want him being
compared to Jeong-yo?
Or is there… another reason?
Who told you they would compare him
to Jeong-yo?
I'm afraid that if we push him right now,
it'll make things worse.
Do you…
just not have any more faith in Pi-o?
If we just give him some space, he'll get
back on his feet on his own.
Don't even bother bringing up
the concerto to him again.
He'll get out of his slump in his own
damn time.
Oh, jeez…
Wait.
Is she seriously still bothered by
Choi Jeong-yo?
Is it because of the rumors?
NCAPF STEERING COMMITTEE MEMBER
KANG JI-HYE
This… is really strange.
Or could it be
a coincidence?
INCOMING CALL
010-0528-8105
Yes, hello?
Hello Ms. Kang,
my name's Choi Jeong-yo. We met the
other day.
Jeong-yo.
So why did you want to meet with
me here today?
Is it something confidential?
Oh… definitely not.
I'm just a bit concerned that the Hankook
Symphony Orchestra might be
at a disadvantage because of me.
I will show
what I'm capable of. You'll see.
Would you please reconsider the budget?
Wow, Jeong-yo,
you're just so considerate.
All right.
I'll move on this right now and they'll
take another look.
- Hmm…
- Thank you.
Jeong-yo, regarding your memory loss…
How are you doing? Is there a lot you
have forgotten about?
Is it just the time around the accident
that you can't recall?
Or do you not remember your
childhood as well?
I don't remember anything before
the accident.
So…
all the things that you went through
with Pi-o in school…
what happened during the competition…
So you don't even remember your parents,
do you?
No.
But you've seen
a doctor, haven't you?
Did they tell you anything about bringing
your memory back?
They said it's nearly impossible.
They said that?
Not even with some kind of trigger?
By any chance,
is there anything about my parents
that you could tell me?
If you know anything at all, I'd love to
know.
Anything, really.
Your mom died… you were…
ten years old.
She died of a brain hemorrhage right in
the concert hall
where you had competed earlier.
I was the one who called emergency
services for her.
So you can imagine how much I care about
you.
Oh, I'm so sorry, ma'am.
N
Thank you for this.
That means
that I was not abandoned…
or despised by my parents, after all.
You know, that…
That was what I actually feared the most.
N
Do you mind if I ask you
one more question?
Are you also against Mr. Pi-o and me
performing a concerto together?
Oh…
It's not that I'm against it.
But what if pushing him
back onto the stage now
only ends up making things worse for him.
Tell me
what's your reason?
This is your big debut…
I'm sure it's incredibly important.
So why choose Pi-o?
That is the reason I chose him.
It's a really big moment for me.
I watched a video of your son performing.
And I loved it.
A pianist of his caliber
on stage with me…
would be an absolute dream come true.
It felt like I had discovered
a rare treasure that's hard to find.
From what I know, this slump started
after a mistake at a recital.
It's nearly impossible to overcome
the yips, like that, with a solo
performance.
But in a concerto, there's someone
there to support him through it.
If possible, would you mind speaking to
your son
just one last time.
I'm…
confident I can help Pi-o overcome
this slump for good.
I'm glad we had the chance to do this.
Let's do this again sometime.
- Thank you for your time.
- Have a good night.
You too.
Pi-o, it's mom.
Can I come in?
Go ahead.
How are you doing, honey?
Is there something you want from me?
It's just that I…
met with Jeong-yo earlier.
Oh… but what for?
He really wants to perform a concerto
with you. And asked me to convince you.
He said he was captivated
by your playing after watching a video of
your performance.
He doesn't want the world ending up
without your music.
It's… really moving isn't it?
I'm very aware…
that you have conflicting feelings
about him.
But I think this might actually be
a good opportunity and it's worth a try.
At the end of the day, a concerto is less
stressful than a solo recital,
and if you think about it,
you and Jeong-yo had really great
chemistry.
Mom, are you trying to tell me
what to do?
I won't force you if you really
don't want to do it, but I'd like you
to give it some thought, will you?
Well, all I can do is give you my two
cents.
At the end of the day, it's your choice.
MARTIN VOGEL
How long is this gonna take?
I think it'll take some time. You have
to be patient.
JAE-IN
You know Hye-jeong's piano trio
concert is coming up, right?
Pi-yo,
Wanna go see it?
Oh!
There you are.
Oh…
Hye-jeong
invited Jeong-yo to the performance.
My dear… you came.
- Thank you for showing up.
- Don't mention it.
I came because I haven't seen a
performance in a while.
Oh, yeah?
When would you have come
to see a performance with Yoon Han-rim
in it?
Come on, admit it,
you came for my sake, didn't you?
Hm! Jeong-yo.
Hey.
How was the performance?
- Was it any good?
- It was nice.
- Yeah.
- I liked all three of them.
The ensemble was good too.
All three of them are from our alma mater.
They're all music majors from our grade.
Ah.
But who was…
the one playing the piano just now?
I thought he was really good.
Hmm. Good in what way?
I thought he was forcing it.
Really?
Jeong-yo! Jeong-yo!
Hey, Jeong-yo! Whoa! Hey! Oh, look at you.
Man…
you know how worried sick all of our
classmates were when you disappeared?
I forgot…
you have no memories from back then.
Oh.
For sure you don't remember that you
and me used fight all the time in school.
I used to fight?
Oh, yeah!
I mean, we were just teenagers full of
adrenaline and hormones back then,
we were just young, so we fought a lot.
It's okay, man. Kids become friends by
fighting and stuff, you know that.
Oh, dude…
I heard you joined the Hankook Symphony
Orchestra as a conductor.
- I start early next month.
- Oh… who are you performing with?
I still haven't decided.
Well… Then how about me?
I'd much rather play in a big stage
that in a tiny venue like this.
Man… I'll be open with you.
I was deeply moved by you
when I saw you conduct for the
first time.
Hmm,
to be perfectly honest, I think we could
make great music together.
I think we should join forces.
Okay, I'll think about it.
Great, thanks, man.
Hey, Jeong-yo, about the soloist…
we should discuss it a bit more--
Hey, Hong Jae-in.
Trying to interfere
with my sales pitch again?
Huh?
If the pianist and the conductor
are on the same page, then that's that.
Hey, ladies… coming for drinks?
- Okay, but just a few.
- Fine, we'll be there.
All right then, it's at Luce Beers.
Join us there later. You better come,
okay?
I booked us
some tables at Luce Beers for a nightcap.
Don't go home just yet.
Come for a drink and we can go over it
a little bit more. Are you coming?
Sure.
Great. See you in a bit. Yeah. Ha…
All of you better be there! I'll be
waiting.
- Of course! We'll be there.
- We're coming! See you in a bit.
Are you really considering
performing with him?
Listen, I know it's not my place to say
this, but he's not your guy.
His music lacks soul and honestly,
so does he.
Do you really want someone like that
to perform with you for your debut?
I think you should reconsider
your choice.
Is that so?
Then why don't you do the concerto
with me, so I don't have to perform
with him?
I would much rather perform with you,
Mr. Pi-o.
I watched a video of your performance,
and it was spectacular.
And I'm asking you to do this
because performing with you would make
me look good.
What do you mean by that?
The Hankook Symphony Orchestra is
notorious for being territorial.
Since I was brought in unexpectedly,
I still have a lot to do to prove
myself to them.
If you do this, it would really
help me out big time.
I understand what you're saying, but the
thing is,
I still haven't gotten over my slump,
I told you--
It's just something you'll have to face
sooner or later.
Mr. Pi-o.
I think it will be really good.
N
I would much rather perform with you,
Mr. Pi-o.
If you do this, it would really
help me out big time.
It's just something you'll have to face
sooner or later.
KANG PI-O
I'm in. Let's do it.
In the end, I guess you got
what you wanted.
I told you this was risky, but you don't
listen.
With all due respect, I don't think
it'll be risky.
I whole-heartedly believe that
Mr. Kang-Pio is the best partner for a
successful debut.
What about the program?
Hm?
You said the second half would be
Brahms One, the piece that won you the
conducting competition.
And the first half?
Have the two of you already
agreed on that?
Um… actually, we haven't yet…
What do you want to play?
Have you thought about it?
Ravel. That's what I would like to play.
No, that would just muddy the theme.
How about Mozart's Piano Concerto Twenty
instead?
From a storytelling standpoint,
it shows you coming out of the darkness
and into the light.
So pairing Mozart Twenty and Brahms
One would actually keep
- the overall program more cohesive.
- But think about it,
Pi-o has never played Mozart Twenty
before, and as you know,
it is not exactly an easy piece--
What are you saying?
Are professionals only supposed to
play what they already know?
Hm.
Well,
if you feel, like we might be pushing it,
I don't mind performing something
- you've--
- No.
I know I can do it.
I will do it.
N
ENSEMBLE ROOM
Are you sure you can do it?
Because if you think it might be too
much--
Do you think it's too much?
I told you I could do it.
What made you think this would be a good
idea?
He was so adamant about it that I finally
gave in. But if he ends up ruining
his debut because of this--
What do you think is unique about
Choi Jeong-yo's way of doing things?
It's the audacity to do the impossible.
That's his charm.
And the sheer ferocity
with which he manages to pull it off.
And if he doesn't?
We'll deal with the aftermath of that.
The orchestra's eightieth is coming up.
It's now time that a new conductor
showed up and took over.
So we should use this
as a chance to see whether Choi Jeong-yo
is capable of doing that.
Excuse me…
I reserved a practice  room.
Uh…
- You can go to Room Three if you'd like.
- Thanks.
Hey.
Do you know who just came
to practice here?
Kang Pi-o himself!
- What?
- This is insane!
Guess what Kang Pi-o is playing
right now.
He's playing Hanon One.
HEY, THIS IS INSANE
GUESS WHAT KANG PI-O IS PLAYING RIGHT NOW
HAHAHAHAHA
IS KANG PI-O AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL KID?
What brings you all the way here?
Choi Jeong-yo.
I'm really sorry,
but I need your help.
I've been trying to overcome it,
but I can't.
I don't know how, but I memorized
the piece,
but I'm still completely terrified
of having to perform
in front  of people.
And I… don't have the slightest idea
how to overcome it.
I don't care if I ruin my reputation,
but  I won't  drag you  down with  me.
If you decide I won't be able to do it,
find someone else.
Do you have some free time right now?
I want to take you somewhere.
I just happened to hear him
playing one day on the subway.
He usually out here around this time
on the weekends.
Isn't it something?
To hear a performance like this out here?
Mr. Pi-o, why do you think people even
listen to music?
Because it offers us some comfort in
the crazy chaos of life.
And do you think the people listening
to this music right now
are standing here judging him by any
chance?
They're not.
They're all being comforted by him.
But what I need you to look at closely
now
is the expression on his face.
Does he look like
he's afraid of being judged by the
audience?
He does not.
Not at all.
The thing is…
he's finding joy in the very music
he's playing.
Because he's the one
being comforted by his music more than
anyone.
Has something
happened recently that's been bothering
you?
Maybe… something broke inside you
and your slump might've started there.
I'm sure you know that before playing
for anyone else, you have to play for
yourself.
Before you can even think of comforting
anyone,
you need to figure out how
to soothe your own…
wounds and heal your heart.
To start out,
try playing music for yourself,
to comfort your heart.
Tell me the truth.
Just tell me who his father is.
And send him back to that bastard!
I've told you already, why don't you
believe me.
He doesn't have a father.
Pi-o is
a gift sent to me by God. He's a miracle.
Oh, my goodness, you've lost your mind.
You're insane!
You have gone completely mad!
N
Maybe… something broke inside you
and your slump might've started there.
Mr. Kang Pi-o, have you ever… just played
music to comfort your own heart?
I'm sure you know that before playing for
anyone else, you have to play for
yourself.
Before you can even think of comforting
anyone,
you need to figure out how to soothe
your own wounds…
You're all checked in. Have a good
evening.
2026 KOREA LUCENA GRAND AWARDS
That's great!
- Good to see you.
- Oh, hi!
- It's been forever.
- Yeah, way too long.
- Where's your seat?
- I'll pin it on you.
It's further up.
I'll see you later then. I will,  won't I?
- Oh, hello sir.
- Ah, yes, hello.
How have you been?
- Oh, hello.
- How long has it been since the last time?
Ah…
- It feels like just the other day. Yes.
- I know, right?
You're doing well, I hope?
Jeong-yo, nice to see you here.
- It's a pleasure to see you.
- Oh. Hello Ms. Kang.
- Hello.
- Gosh, Ms. Yoon.
You should have told me in advance
that you were going to bring Jeong-yo
with you.
Since you could not provide the subsidy,
what choice did I have but to send
the man of the hour in search for
sponsors?
Though it's hardly a musician's job.
If you put it like that, Jeong-yo might
misunderstand you.
I've been working myself to the bone
for the Hankook Symphony Orchestra
- lately.
- Ms. Yoon.
Oh, my. Hello, director!
When did you get here?
- Just a moment ago…
- What on earth did you do?
His playing sounds completely different
now.
He's just been playing nonstop as of
late,
but something's different now.
I can feel the joy in his music.
What have you done?
That's Pi-o's hard work finally
paying off.
Sure… did you see what I sent you?
Oh, yes I did.
Distinguished guests, honored attendees,
and the award winners who are the
stars of this event.
It is a great honor to deliver this
congratulatory address at such a
meaningful event.
The name Lucena
means "a shining companion of the arts,
even in the darkest of times"
Art is a delicate flower that always
blooms from the deepest parts of the
human soul.
- However, for that flower to fully
- Excuse me for a second.
Bloom in society,
it will definitely need
- Hm-hmm.
- someone's care and attention.
He's just been playing nonstop
as of late,
but something's different now.
I can feel the joy in his music.
What have you done?
Let's just play again. What do you think?
Okay.
Hey, don't be sore if I beat you, okay?
When we play, let's have fun!
Oh, please. I'm the one who's gonna win.
So you can't get upset.
PERFORMERS' GREEN ROOM
THIS WAY
Let's be real, I'm clearly
in first place.
You know it.
- Hmm…
- Hey.
- You wish.
- I'm gonna win.
Jeong-yo.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I…
I went to the restroom and couldn't
find my way back.
Then I happened to spot the piano,
so I just came in to see it.
It's like
it's somewhat familiar.
This place hasn't changed
much since then.
Is there
anything you remembered?
No.
Why?
Nothing…
Shall we go?
Hey, Pi-o.
How've you been?
You haven't changed.
Man, Han-rim and I were completely shocked
you were doing the concerto.
What's that supposed to mean?
You know…
there…
were these rumors going around that you
were involved with Choi Jeong-yo's
disappearance somehow.
So when we heard you were
here
we were like, "Huh?
That's so weird.”
Who the hell's saying that crap?
Whoa. So scary…
If you were not, then great.
Oh, my, what vulgar language
from someone so classy.
At rehearsal today
try… not to mess up.
Good luck.
Wow, look at him.
Unbelievable.
- Is he okay? He doesn't look good.
- He doesn't seem confident.
- What's his problem?
- I mean, you've heard about it, right?
- He shouldn't be here.
- Can he even play now?
It's the worst possible thing really.
Gosh, you know what, I jut really
don't get it.
I mean, I get that he's Kang Pi-o
and all that, but why would anyone book
a soloist who's in a slump?
- Exactly.
- I know, right?
Well, his family's rich, you know?
- Hello.
Hello.
Cellos, you're slightly ahead.
Make sure you come in right on
the piano's final note.
Okay.
The piano's all over the place.
What do we do then?
Pianist Kang Pi-o.
At the cutoff, make sure the next
downbeat lands exactly on time.
Understood.
Again.
Start from the piano solo.
N
I mean, it's not like he's bad,
but doesn't he feel a little shaky?
And he plays it differently every
single time.
Maybe he's not completely out of his
slump just yet, you know?
Well…
There's always a period of transition.
Yeah, but why do we have to bear the
brunt of his period of transition?
To be honest, I just don't get it.
Choi Jeong-yo and Kang Pi-o
are every bit as arrogant and
insufferable now as they were when we
were back in school.
Why are you still here?
Rehearsal ended quite a while ago.
Hey.
Why did you ask me to perform with you?
It feels like everyone…
is waiting for me to crash and burn
whenever I play.
Holding on to my confidence is getting
harder to do.
So what made you…
believe I'd be able to pull this off?
N
Hm…
I don't know.
But I think they might be acting that way
because they're reacting more to me
than to you.
It seems to me, that we have no one
but each other to count on.
N
When I was at the monastery,
I had a really bad case of
social anxiety.
I could barely be around people, but I
so desperately wanted to play music.
N
So I created
an orchestra that only existed in my
imagination.
I had conversations with them. I even
argued with them.
As it turned out… N
That was the greatest weapon a conductor
could have.
And that's because any good conductor…
needs to have everything figured out
way before stepping in front of the
orchestra.
Mr. Pi-o, if fear keeps creeping in,
map it all out in your head, in detail.
Then at some point,
this fear you're feeling, will completely
fade away.
I know it's not easy,
but you'll have to trust me implicitly.
Because I'm the one guiding the
orchestra.
Would you like to hear the music in my
imagination?
Oh, if you don't mind,
a piano would be helpful.
Violin.
Pianissimo.
Cello, bass.
- Oboe, flute,
- Espressivo!
Timpani, forte!
Piano.
Con dolore.
That was amazing!
How are you doing?
Oh,
thank you for coming out to the
performance today.
Hm-hmm.
I'd appreciate it if you could write an
article about it.
Oh, of course! It'll be my pleasure.
Yes, of course. Let's keep in touch.
Hmm.
Hi, I'm back.
Oh, my gosh, it was so emotional.
I was literally holding back tears
at the end.
How do you two manage to touch my heart
every single time!
I want to thank both of you
for helping me all the way through.
Oh, not at all.
I was really scared up there tonight.
But I was absolutely blown away by how
well you performed.
Oh, wait!
Let's do something with the two of you
for the anniversary festival.
But you've gotta perform together!
I wanna take this opportunity, and turn
you into a brand. What do you say?
I don't know…
Oh.
Whoa, with all these calls…
we're barely getting to talk today!
Give me a sec?
HI, it's Jae-in.
Mr. Pi-o.
Hmm?
Now that our performance has ended
successfully,
there's something that I'd like to say.
So…
By any chance--
Oh…
I found out who was behind the order
to kidnap Choi Jeong-yo.
What is it?
Did something happen?
Oh… not at all.
Do you mind?
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
Mom, why did you do it?
We have to confess to Jeong-yo and beg
for forgiveness.
- I won't go!
- If the truth comes out,
not only will my life be over, but yours
too.
Why that look on your face?
Are you hiding something from me?
I didn't have the courage to tell the
truth back then.
What if he's up to something?
I'm worried out of my mind that you keep
getting mixed up with him at every turn.
I'm sure he's hiding something.
At the Hermione International
Competition…